Hey folks.
I built something new.
I built it for myself,
but I think you're gonna like it too.
So hear me out.
All of us love movies, right?
But sometimes it's just
hard to find one movie to watch.
There are like so many
of them and it's like
even harder when it's the two of you,
right?
What you might like.
She might not like what
she might like, you might not like,
right?
What's the solution?
The solution is a very
simple but neat trick
isWhere I surface you.
Tender like interface.
What for movies.
So you swipe left or
right on the movies.
Both of you individually.
And the movies that both of you like.
End up being a short list.
So guys Pick a movie, not a fight.
Do let me know what you think of it.
Try it out in the link.